{
    "subject": "resource/Cecil_Turner",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1944-04-02",
    "human_readable": "Cecil Turner was born on April 2, 1944.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8474321365356445,
            "question": "When was Cecil Turner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7092760801315308,
            "question": "What month was Cecil Turner born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6399367451667786,
            "question": "What day of the month was Cecil Turner born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6005964279174805,
            "question": "What significant event might have happened in the world the year Cecil Turner was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5580452680587769,
            "question": "How old is Cecil Turner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43292659521102905,
            "question": "Is Cecil Turner's birthday in the spring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4069771468639374,
            "question": "In what year did Cecil Turner come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3866201937198639,
            "question": "What is the numerical value representing Cecil Turner's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33461275696754456,
            "question": "Could Cecil Turner be a Baby Boomer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06767904758453369,
            "question": "Does April fall within the first half of the year?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cecil Turner was born on April 2, 1944.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1942_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Cecil Turner be a Baby Boomer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1942_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the numerical value representing Cecil Turner's birthdate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1942_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Cecil Turner come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1942_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1942_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1942/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1942/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt, Cecil Turner's birthdate is mentioned as April 2, 1944.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1942/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt, Cecil Turner's birthdate is mentioned as March 15, 1928.\n\nHowever, there is no information in any of the files that contradicts the statement \"Cecil Turner was born on April 2, 1944\". Therefore:\n\nResponse: {'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Cecil Turner was born on April 2, 1944.\" Specifically, both `66.txt` and `20.txt` mention his birth date as April 2, 1944."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}